The shocking turn of events as usual guys
No, I really don't I
I try I think it wherever people says seriously, but then I know you know like when Alex talks about his theories and stuff
Yeah, I'd like you know, I'll listen and I'll okay
But I'll try to say hey Alex
You're a little bit off. It's like, you know
Sometimes I items you I got I spoke a little bit part my pizza brush. I just take a shower you fool
You go brush your ass
Okay, I might I'm clean. Oh my look like it. No kind of three already, but look
God damn my nails get dirty fast, huh?
Okay, well, I mean
I rather this like
Yeah, we have a new okay, so guys the rules are the screen so Sam it okay, so Sam I know you like the n-word, okay?
Which so we're not we're not doing that even though even the soft I don't want to get into babe at the stop a the heart a
Okay, the problem is Sam and I just have
everybody okay
everybody three diamond, you know Tony beta and
some
10 other people I even know
Trying to say oh, let's listen. Let's like false flag is channelists. Let's do all this. Okay, so I'm trying not to
Just have a reason it's like if anything goes wrong on my channel. I want to be my fault
You know if it's like so I can blame myself. I don't want to say oh
I don't want to be I'd rather have it my fault. I did something rather than my fault that I just
Was be trying to be nice with somebody let them on the panel and they they did something trying to hurt me
And it's like yeah, so
Okay, whatever salmon is
Remember salmon is I he's a human being. Yeah, we're human beings at
At the end of the day at the end of the day, we're all human beings, okay?
I'm sorry for that 30 that was in love. Okay. I was a loving invitation at the end of the day
Like I like how she does it actually
It is my link, but um, okay, so ray ray raise that you ray
First of all the panel before that you started saying
Death to some other some country that I don't say that again. He didn't say that it was you
Saying that he said he said it a few times and you're absolutely just like something you just didn't say
I don't know if you understand YouTube and I know some people don't
No, okay. There's only like a few percent of them even have a channel. Okay. I
Get at home see I'm happy. Where's just one minute. Okay, so and Ray so and then you said
You've seen the end where I left the I was I was sitting there watching I was listening
I was even watching the city to see what would have happened and then it would be I'm gone for 10 seconds
Literally, and you're saying the end with the heart. So it's a great. There's a problem
There's a problem. So if that ever happens again, Ray, you're going in my book and say I'm a you're going my book
You're learning about you okay before Santa comes on family woman, but I'll be you're already in my beta. Oh my gosh
You're in my book. I'm
I'm dedicating a whole couple pages to be actually
Isn't it in a nice way? It's not a nice way. She thinks I'm she thinks I'm like some evil
wicked
hateful selfish person. I don't know. Do I have my mic on even? Hold on. Oh my god
Okay guys, did you hear where it is said?
Run away again. Okay. Yeah, how about how about just like kick Rob out?
How about if I kick that person Rob out like who's nothing anything to anybody in my chat
It's like it's like a usual so I don't know if you heard you guys you didn't hear anything
It's okay. Go guys. Everyone go over to be this go over beat us. No, it's like guys
Do it I've got well, I don't have my phone handy. Can I mod please ban Rob? Just go ahead and just mute him
He hasn't he hasn't probably a hundred other accounts. It's not gonna do anything. He'll be back. He'll be very interesting
You know, it was doing probably more annoying, but
Yeah, he asked for it. Okay, so I'm here. I'm writing. Hold on. I'm gonna write
Not right. I'm
Rob, if I write your name on book, I'm just gonna cross out you win. Okay. I'm writing Rob. I'm gonna do the capital r small o the bg
I'm gonna
That's your name, Rob. There you go. It's all crossed out deep. It's been how angrily it crossed out
What did you miss? Oh nothing nothing happened. I'm dripping with success. Oh my god. I'm dripping with more than that, baby
Come on Q. Okay. So anyway, so I'm gonna write Q. I write Q and but there's nothing I have nothing else to write about him right now
I'm just wearing Q. Okay. I see it's almost unbelievable. So, okay
It almost unbelievable. Oh, yeah, I mean you're a fluid diamond. I was I just gonna I'm gonna wait. I only do on God
Wednesday, I'm sorry, Ilya. Ilya.
And I'm gonna like do not mod.
Because Ilya, Ilya, and I do love you and you're funny and I love your wig and your your Russian accent.
You showed you showed your butthole the first time you were on.
And then I said, okay, then he's like, oh, can I please pee in a bucket on your shirt?
And I said, I said, no, please. This don't pee on the bucket, please. The next, as soon as I turn my head for a second,
I hear, I hear a peeing sound, okay? And then you showed your red rock. It was like a red rocket, but it was, I don't know, it was more of a red,
what did it look like?
But bottle rockers guys guys guys please please please guys guys come on come on guys guys guys please please no threats
No threats come on guys no hate speech no no hate speech no dogs and come on guys guys, please come on
Come on I mean come on come on come on. No slow slander come on. No nudity. Please please guys respect the host and out of the pan
Yeah, yeah, exactly. Thank you. Thank you for the public service announcement God. Oh, you know
Okay, just 10% I need commercially make with that. Okay, so
No one cares just swimming out in the ocean like you promised. Okay. You got you got you know, right?
Rob is so me as you Rob is Rob is like
Tell me this woman on the middle of the ocean. I didn't promise you
I you know Ariel was gonna pick me up and take me like an island Catalina's right here. Okay, wasn't gonna drown in the ocean
He wasn't that good. I mean, yeah, if you I can I can put I can put God's picture, but I have one here
I don't know. It's okay. It's not a piece of my book. Oh, oh my god
God's that and Q. Oh my god. Get ready to end this dream again. Okay, cute
You're gonna call me the n-word. You're gonna you're gonna show me your fake dick or something. What's gonna happen tonight?
What are you doing? Why do you look like?
What do you look like?
What are you doing? No, you're not going to you. You look different. Thank you. Thank you
Hello, oh
This is a treat
So cute you are
For you you're doing your kind of you're kind of sexy cute. You're a good looking guy
Like really I like that's I like it Harry chef. Oh my gosh. Oh my gosh. Oh, is that wonderful you guys
That's what's called. That's what's called the vine intervention when he shows you that and it's like a brother there work
Yes, oh my god
Jordin Jordin says she Jordin says she knows cute. I don't know who Jordin is but Jordin says
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Please
The person that says that word or name is the accuser friend of hers. No, it's like that's that's a dog
Posh can't strike you from the chat. They know you cannot
I
Stop crying damn
Bitch ass nigga, okay, everybody's dead mom you crying about a dox
Nursing that's used called deflection
Which is like take something that they're actually doing and accuse everybody else of it and
And then we'll see like oh, he'd never be capable of that because he
Well, cue doc's everybody cue doc's family members
Hey, hey, can you please hide that person? Let's say yeah, please please your mom, please get a mod
Please get up one mod. Please
Name grow the fuck up
Picture I'm not crying. I just cooked the content
You can't strike or for a chat you don't fuck
Hi
Cry cry cry
Viewers accused as I basically started but anyway, that's besides
Say you don't have to worry about that. You I don't know why you weren't
He can get $15 he can't strike you for nothing
I'm not talking about that. I'm not talking. I'm not even talking about that part of it. I'm just talking about you know it in general
Okay, I don't know why you give this white boy power this white boys homeless
Bumman's white boy is homeless. He can't strike nothing. He don't even have a computer to get stuck
I see I think it's Gary. I appreciate that. Okay. I appreciate it. I just give you my phone
He's like screaming like a bit
Thank you, I saw I can read your lips what he was saying you came on and then he was like
But his record was not but he didn't know and so I could see his lips move and I can kind of read lips a little bit
And then it was just talking about your bullshit about
Hey, hold on shade shade. I don't go at Q's mom
Tell that shit to Q. Tell that shit to the white Jimmy. Who said he wanted a great kids not me
okay
Hannah is Hannah. Don't blame me. Tell that shit to Q's say get the fuck out of here. Thanks. Thanks, Hannah. Thanks